Contact

+919972413758 (Home) dandagi.arjun95@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/arjundandagi (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Python (Programming Language)
Docker Products
Java

Languages

English

Hindi

Kannada

Certifications

AWS Certified Solutions Architect – Associate

Bash Scripting and Shell programing
The Neuroscience of Learning
AWS Certified Developer - Associate

Completion Award for Oracle MOOC: Managing Java Cloud Services Using REST

Arjun Dandagi

DevOps AWS | Python | Terraform | Packer | Docker | Jenkins | Ansible | ELK | Rancher | Kubernetes | Bash

Bengaluru, Karnataka, India

Summary

Experienced DevOps Developer with a demonstrated history of working in the telecommunications industry. Skilled in Python, Terraform, Docker, Amazon Web Services (AWS), and Java. Strong engineering professional with a Bachelor of Engineering - BE focused on Computer Science from PES University.

Experience

Uninstall.io
DevOps Developer
January 2019 - Present
Bangaon Area, India

Telstra

IT Developer

July 2017 - December 2018 (1 year 6 months)

Hyderabad Area, India

Was part of the Development team at the beginning. working on JAVA technology using SpringBoot to write microservice, learned AWS technology and got certified as AWS Developer Associate.

got interested in docker and technology toolset and thereafter moved to work in

- 1. Docker
- 2. Rancher
- 3. Bamboo
- 4. Bash
- 5. AWS
- 6. Terraform

automated blue-green deployment in rancher via bamboo.

gained a good amount of DevOps toolset. and thought of progressing in career as DevOps :)

GetGo

QA at GetGo (formerly part of citrix) February 2017 - June 2017 (5 months)

Bangalore

worked on a testing framework like Selenium using Java technology. was part of the GOTO webinar team. work on testing attendee reports , schedule timings etc

Education

PES University

Bachelor of Engineering - BE, Computer Science · (2013 - 2017)

Jawahar Navodaya Vidyalaya haveri

· (2006 - 2012)